Hi! My name is Chloe Marianne
嗨！ 我叫克洛伊·玛丽安
a new animator at Psych2Go.
Psych2Go的一个新的漫画制作者
I'm animating this episode for you today. Enjoy!
今天由我来制作这集漫画，好好享受！
Dating is rough for everybody
约会对每个人来说都是艰难的
But is being queer an extra hurdle to jump over in the effort to find love?
但是，在寻找爱情的过程中，身为一名同性恋者是不是格外的艰难？
We at Psych2Go say yes.
Psych2Go觉得的确如此
There are many unique problems that those in the LGBT community face
LGBT群体在他们约会的时候
during their time on the dating scene.
会遇到许多独特的问题
Without further ado
话不多说
here is a list of eight dating problems the LGBT community faces
这里列出了LGBT群体会遇到的八个约会问题
Number one: Casual racism
第一：不经意间的种族歧视
A recent study on gay dating preferences shows that
最近一项关于同性恋约会偏好的研究表明，到目前为止，
80% of black men, 79% Asian men and 75% of South Asian men
有80%的黑人男性，79%的亚洲男性和75%的南亚男性
have all endured racism in their efforts to date
在约会中遭受了种族歧视
Many people of color also experience fetishization
许多有色人种都有着格式化的形象定义
Black men are messaged in the hopes that they'll be aggressive or masculine
黑人男子被认为他们是好斗的或着男性化的
Asian men are often messaged
人们经常发消息给亚洲男人
because they might seem cute or submissive
因为他们看起来很可爱或顺从
How do women compare?
女人怎么比较？
Fairly better, actually.
实际上相对来说好一些
Queer women are less likely to be affected by ethnicity
女同性恋者受族裔影响的可能性较小
and more open to interracial dating.
更容易接受开放的跨种族约会
Number two: Fat and femme shaming
第二：肥胖和性别羞辱
The queer community is full of individuals
这个社区中充满了
with different body types and gendered energies
不同身材和性别魅力的个体
This includes some of us who are a little on the skinny side
这包括我们中的一些人，瘦弱的
or weigh a few extra pounds
或者多重几磅的
Or exude some feminine energy.
或者散发出女性化魅力的
The unfortunate truth is
不幸的是
gay culture does not deem these traits desirable in our world today
同性恋文化并不认为当今世界需要这些特质
Muscles and manliness went over femininity
肌肉和男子气概超越了女性化气质
which many mistakenly consider subordinate and lesser
许多人错误地认为女性化气质是次要的
Number three: Hook up culture
第三：逢场作戏
Believe me
相信我
when you're looking for a hook up
当你正在索取一个联系方式
or a friends-with-benefits type situation
或交一个可以为你带来利益的朋友时
this can be great
这可能是个不错的表现
This is not to say that
这并不是说
there aren't queer people who are searching for a deeper connection
同性恋者不在寻找更深层次的联系
But if you are looking to get to know someone
但如果你想在他们把手伸进你的裤子之前
before they stick their hands down your pants
认识某人
this can be extremely frustrating
这可能是非常令人沮丧的
It's not easy talking to someone you've just met
和你刚认识的一个人交谈并不容易
only for them to ask you about your sexual preferences
当他们只是想知道你的性偏好
and what your genitals look like
和你的生殖器状况时
Number four: Not enough fish in the sea
第四个数字：海里的鱼还不够
Growing up in an urban cityscape can be the best thing in the world
对那些寻求选择的同性恋来说
for a queer person looking for options
在一个城市中生活可能是世界上最好的事情
Whether you're in New York, L.A, Tokyo or London,
无论你是在纽约、洛杉矶、东京还是伦敦
There is endless opportunity for you to find the person of your dreams
你有无限的机会来找到你的梦想中的人
Not in a city packed with people?
不在一个人满为患的城市里吗？
The odds are less in your favor.
那遇到的概率就会小很多了
It's hard for a queer person in a small town
在小镇或人烟稀少的地区
or sparsely populated area to meet potential partners
同性恋者很难与潜在的伴侣见面
Don't give up!
不要放弃！
Dating in a small town does not mean that you're doomed
在小镇上约会并不意味着你注定要失败
Number five: Are they even into you?
第五：他们真的喜欢你吗？
Sure, there are some common tells that
当然，有一些常识
could give us some insight on whether someone is LGBTQ
可以使我们判断关于某人是否是LGBTQ
but sometimes the only way to know is to ask
但有时唯一知道的方法就是问
Is she into women or not?
她是否喜欢女人？
Can you get a guy to fall in love with you
你能让一个男人爱上你
even though he keeps calling you his bro?
即使他一直叫你兄弟吗？
For the LGBTQ community, this is a common obstacle
对于LGBTQ社区来说，这是一个常见的障碍
Number six: Dating while closeted
第六：闭门约会
Let me preface this point by saying that many people choose
首先我要说一下，许多人
to keep their sexual identity a secret for a range of reasons
出于一系列原因选择将他们的性身份保密
including the preservation of their personal safety
包括保护他们的人身安全
That being said, it is hard to date while you are still in the closet.
尽管如此，当你将自己封闭起来的时候，是很难约会的
It can be mentally and emotionally exhausting
保守这个秘密
to keep the person you love a secret
会让你在精神和情感上都筋疲力尽
It can also be just as exhausting for your partner
对你的伴侣来说也同样让他感到精疲力竭
who must help you maintain a double life
你的伴侣必须帮助你维持双重生活
in order for your relationship to continue
以便让你们的关系继续下去
For these reasons
由于这些原因
those who date while in the closet may experience relationships strain
那些闭门约会的人可能会感到人际关系紧张
Number seven: Dating with HIV
第七：与艾滋病患者的约会
HIV is still a huge taboo in the LGBT community today.
艾滋病在今天的LGBT群体中仍然是一个巨大的禁忌
Modern medicine has come a long way over the past few decades
在过去的几十年里，现代医学取得了长足的进步
and HIV is no longer a death sentence
而艾滋病也不再是一个死刑判决
But those who live with HIV positive status are
但是那些患有艾滋病的人
shunned from the dating scene
被拒之门外
because of this same fear
由于同样的恐惧
and the misconceptions many of us have of HIV
以及我们许多人对艾滋病的误解
While it is still important to take safety measures
尽管要采取安全措施仍然很重要
HIV is an obstacle that can be overcome by couples
但艾滋病是伴侣携手可以克服的一个障碍
It is important to remember that people with HIV are not dirty
重要的是，要记住，艾滋病毒感染者并不肮脏
or deserving of their status in any way
无论如何，他们都应该由他们自己的地位
and it's totally possible to have a healthy
而且我们完全可以维持
safe relationship with an HIV-positive individual.
与艾滋病毒阳性个体的一个健康安全的关系
Number eight: Transphobia
第八：跨性别恐惧
Dating can be rough if you're trans
如果你是跨性别者，约会可能会很艰难
Trans and non-binary individuals still receive a great deal of harassment
跨性别的个体和非二元性别的个体仍然会受到大量的骚扰
in regards to their gender, sex and appearance
关于他们的性别、性和外表
Trans and non-binary people also have the added stress of deciding if
跨性别的人和非二元性别的人还面临这更大的压力
and when to disclose their identity to dates and partners
即决定是否以及何时向约会对象和伴侣透露自己的身份
Many trans people who are simply looking to get to know
许多想结识某人的跨性别者
someone often find themselves fetishized
经常发现自己被格式化的定义了
Now, keep in mind the LGBT community is diverse
现在，请记住，LGBT群体是多样化的
and a few of these problems are directed more
其中一些问题更多的是针对特定的问题
to some than they are to others
而不是针对其他问题
The first step to solving these problems is awareness.
解决这些问题的第一步是意识
The LGBT community and its supporters
LGBT群体及其支持者
have the ability to shed light on these issues
都有能力阐明这些问题
so that they can be met with love and acceptance
以便他们就能得到爱和接纳
So, what do you think?
所以你怎么看？
Are there any problems that we've missed?
有什么我们错过的问题吗？
Let us know
请告诉我们一下：
Are there any items on this list
在这个列表上有什么项目
that you feel need their own videos?
你觉得需要他们自己的视频吗？
We at Psych2Go want to hear from you.
我们在Psych2Go希望收到你的来信
Psych2Go has a new section dedicated to LGBT topics
Psych2Go有一个新的章节专门讨论LGBT话题
Click on the link below to read more about this list
点击下面的链接阅读更多关于这个列表的信息
and other LGBT articles created by our new content writer, Alex!
以及我们的新创作者Alex创作的其他LGBT文章！
Don't forget to like, comment and subscribe.
不要忘记喜欢，评论和订阅。
Hey everybody
嘿各位
I just want to give a personal thank you video
我只想给你们一个个人的感谢视频
for you guys for always supporting Psych2Go
感谢你们一直支持Psych2Go
and making this all possible for us.
让这一切对我们来说都成为可能
Our vision is to make psychology as accessible as possible
我们的愿景是使心理学尽可能容易获得
so that it promotes self awareness, and it helps you guys grow.
这样它就能促进自我意识，并帮助你们成长
However, we want to make more content for you guys
然而，我们想为你们做更多的内容
and would love your support
并希望得到您的支持
and buying one of these bracelets for our partner, Introvert Pallas
并为我们的合作伙伴Introvert Pallas购买这些手镯之一
Check out the bracelet.
看看这个手镯
It's pretty cool and it even includes Pluto
很酷，甚至包括冥王星
The link to purchase will all be in the description below
购买的链接将全部在下面的简介中
and I hope you guys have an amazing day
我希望你们今天过得愉快
Bye!
再见！